then learn this one eh
a cardboard and a pen
and today I will show you
a different strategy to build my brand
wait for that bus to pass that stays from time to scene
quickie
gets into gear
O my god of heaven
looks for a member with or without experience
I have paper
the vision
the plan
I can create demand
make sales
you just have to find someone to believe this bro
valeu
has the plan
on demand
I have everything here,
I just need a guy member
let's get out of it here
ok let's go
looking for an ind partner
I built my brownie company
for my brownie company
police passing by looking at the sign bro
has the demand
I already have everything
excuse
thank you thank you brother
tamo together
one more marker here
I'm looking for a member
it could be you
and the difference of my brownie
he is not square
he is an edible skate wheel
valeu
it was too much worth this run
I'm looking for someone who believes my idea
caramba
how legal
selling an idea is not the same thing as selling
paçoquinha
so
I need
exchange 1 idea with 1 person who handles a lot of pit
to be able to help me
I'm going to call him now bro
ask for 1 piece of advice
Valeu Felipe
and then the time
do you have any give 1 pit advice to sell
1 business idea
20 sale
1st thing that I think is fundamental is to do with
that people want to feel belonging
in the product you're selling eh
it's much easier for you to sell anything
sister animal
showed immense gratitude
if you're watching this now and got interested
and wants to get into this with me
or know someone who can invest in this idea
write in the comments there for me
who knows you can become my partner or my partner
and together we can be happy
enough to be happy
he was a little pissed right Caião
be happy old
what a shit